Number
one, decide what you want.
Okay? So, just decide
for next 3 months
uh what do you want to to reach? Okay.
Should be a little bit
difficult but not impossible.
Okay. I was at MIT last few days ago.
Somebody say I want to be US president
in 3 months.
I said there's no election this year.
So don't push it.
Okay. Should be possible. Okay.
Okay. I had one guy in
Shanghai. He he came to me after talk.
I met you last year.
You taught me last year
four steps.
Yeah. I don't like it. I said what's the
problem? You said if I do the four steps
I will get it.
And I said what what did you what was
your goal? I don't remember. This is I
met 18,000 people last
year. I said I I don't remember. What is
your
goal? He said I I'm supposed to make $10
million.
Then I did the four
steps. Then I say, "Did you really do
the four steps?"
Did you do number one? Yes. Yes. Number
two. Yes. Yes. Number three. Yes. Yes.
Number four.
Pretty good. Pretty
good. Then I said, "What's the problem?
I didn't make $10 million.
What happened? I only make $7 million.
[Music]
I said, "This is not a problem.
This is okay."
Okay. For 3 months, it's okay.
Okay. He didn't do all four. All right.
Okay. So, number one, decide what you
want.
Okay. What do you want? Okay. One
sentence.
Very clear.
shouldn't say maybe I want
or I want this and this and this and
this
this just pick one
why this uh 3 month is experiment
time pick one thing you want
and make it clear
then if it works
then use it for 100
things. But this is a test. The three
month is a
test. Try one
thing. Focus on one
thing. If with these four
steps, if it works,
then you do it with many
things. Okay? But the
experiment just one thing.
Step number two,
you must find someone else who wants the
same thing or almost the same thing.
So if I want to make
$1
million then what kind of person I have
to find?
Somebody who wants to make almost the
same
Okay. It doesn't help if I find someone
who wants a a horse.
Okay. It has to be similar.
They want to make $800,000 or they want
to make $15 million.
Okay. Then many people told me, I don't
know anybody who wants the same thing.
Then I say check for 24 hours. Talk to
me
[Music]
tomorrow. I found 10 people want to see
you.
Okay, just look for 24
hours among all your friends and your
family.
There's a somebody who wants the same
thing.
That's step number two.
Okay. Number
three, give them one hour at a coffee
shop every week to help them get what
they want.
Okay? So, I like to say
Friday
afternoon, take them to the coffee shop,
then just one hour, help them, okay? To
get what they
want. Okay? That's planting the seed.
Those three are planting the
seed. Okay? If you don't want to help
another person, you cannot use this
system.
Okay? You must find another
person and you must take them out. I
like coffee shop. It's a neutral place.
It's not your house. It's not my house.
It's neutral.
That's step number three.
If you plant a seed, it can maybe stay
in your mind for 10 years without
opening. That's why so many nice people
don't get
result. My mother helps
everybody. She planted many many
seeds. But she didn't put water
on. Okay. So, step number four, you must
do step number
four. If you don't want to do number
step number four, you have to wait for
10 years or 20 years.
Okay? Maybe you will die before that
seat
opens. So, how to put water on the
seed? Me and Stanley going to show you.
Okay. at night, come home, cook your
dinner,
tell your husband to wash the dishes.
Okay, then uh take your shower,
put on your night
clothes, then time for
meditation. Okay, like this. Left foot
first, then right
foot. Okay, like this.
[Music]
Okay. No, I'm kidding.
This is special meditation.
Are you ready? One. E. All right. Start.
Okay. Like that.
I want you to do this meditation like
that on your pillow.
So, you need your pillow and you put
your head on the pillow.
Okay. Then in the meditation you're
supposed to think about
something. What are you supposed to
think
about? Think about the seed which you
planted today or
five in your mind. Oh today in the
afternoon I took my friend to the coffee
[Music]
shop for 1 hour. I help them discuss
their business
[Music]
plan or discuss how they're going to get
a
boyfriend or discuss what to do about
their breast
cancer. Okay? Like
that when you think about
it, the good thing you
did say,
are you from British Airways?
Where you put the thought, the chi will
follow.
This is a very famous Buddhist
thing. Christine Walsh, the
psychologist. Walsh. I said, "Where are
you going next?" This is last couple
years ago.
She said, "I have to take a flight."
I said, "Where are you going?" "Oh, I'm
going to Beijing."
"Why?" "I have to talk to 800 Chinese
psychologists." Then I said, "What's
your plan? What do you want?" She showed
me a
bag. It looks like 800 band-aids.
I said, "You're going to cut their
finger and then give them a band-aid."
No, no, this is not a band-aid.
This is a
thermometer. Then it's like 10 cents or
something.
It only works one hour or
something. Then I said, "Why you buy 800
thermometers?
I'm going to teach them.
Put the thermometer on your finger.
Focus on the finger.
The chi will come from the heart to the
finger and the temperature will go
up. Okay? Where you put your
mind, the chi will go there
and the temperature go up.
So if you think about the good seed you
planted this
afternoon at the Starbucks,
that seed will heat up
and it will open
faster. Okay? So you have to do step
number four.
We call coffee
meditation. It means you can drink some
tea or coffee,
relax. So just think about the good
thing you did.
Okay, it's so easy.
Somebody told me in
Germany, this is too
easy. I said if something is super
correct, if something is correct, it
should
be it should be easy.
If you know what you're doing, something
is easy.
like those uh famous golf
players, they're just
like that's easy for them because they
they know what they're
doing. If you know what you're doing,
making money, finding boyfriend, fixing
your cancer,
being
happy, it should be easy.
Okay, if you're using correct
system, it should be easy. What's more
easy than
this? Just think, okay, they say, what
are you doing?
I'm making $200 million.
Where? Where? What's your secret?
My pillow.
Okay. Like that. Just relax.
Think about the good thing you did.
No
pride. Pride. Pride is what?
I'm the best seed planter in the world.
Not like that.
just like, "Oh, yeah. Uh, so I had a
problem with my girlfriend."
Step number one, I have I want to fix a
problem with my girlfriend.
Step number two, find a person who has a
problem with their girlfriend. There's
about one billion. Okay.
Okay. Step number three,
take them to Starbucks.
It will also help American
economy. Take them to Starbucks
and just help them. You know, I heard
you're having trouble with your
girl. I I'm also having
trouble. Then let's meet once a
week. Let's talk about what we can do.
You must spend 1 hour a week.
If you don't want to spend one hour a
week if you don't want to find another
person you cannot use the system
then don't ask me next year to teach
you.
Okay? If you don't want to use it then I
will go home and take some rest. Okay?
Okay. It's your job now.
Plant the seed.
Decide what you want.
Find the person who wants it.
Help them for one hour a week.
Step number
four. Put water on the seat. If you
don't put water on the seed, maybe it
will take 100 years to open.
Okay? Just
relax. Put the chi on the seat.
Today I did a nice job.
I help somebody.
Okay, that's all that will that will
make the seat open faster.
You see good people, nothing good
happened to them.
Oh, this guy helped the poor
[Music]
people. But he always has financial
problem. Gisha, I think your system
doesn't
work. He didn't do number four.
Okay. He didn't know about it.
Okay.